WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
The pay-as-you-throw waste system rollout
is causing ongoing confusion.
Fearing they'll have to pay
to dispose of trash,
people are throwing away things
they don't need to.
How could I just throw it away?
I spent money
and sent it off out of respect.
Residents are putting up warning signs
over trash dumping…
It's so hot! Come on, hurry!
It's so hot.
WEDDING INVITATION
Too many home appliances…
I had to rip the limbs off the stuffed toy
so it would fit
in that designated trash bag.
It just felt so wrong.
Don't you even have kimchi?
Everyone knows my engagement is off?
Hey, what in the world do you eat?
-How do you survive on this?
-Life goes on for the living.
That's enough already.
Your mom called me again.
Seems like she's checking if you're alive.
You heard of pain spots?
You know, where you feel pain.
Our organs have pain spots too.
All our internal organs have them.
A broken heart
isn't just a figure of speech.
It actually hurts.
My heart
clenches
painfully.
It's true.
Call your family, you ungrateful brat.
I could no longer meet
my best friend of seven years,
but my best friend of 20 years
was still looking only at me.
Is everything really okay?
How about food?
You must be out of side dishes.
Should I go?
I made a lot of jangjorim.
Even married couples can part ways.
Remarkable people always
live their own way.
By the way… haven't you heard from him?
All right, I won't mention him.
Okay, go on, get some sleep.
Forget what exactly?
Did she say that again?
All she ever says is, "Forget it"
or "You don't need to know."
I wish she'd talk to me.
I wish she'd open up to me.
Well, she thinks she's a grown-up now.
What else is a mother for?
Who's gonna worry about her more than me?
Are you sad
she's not looking for Mom anymore?
She used to only look for me.
Now I'm the only one she doesn't tell.
She's shutting me out.
Traitor.
Where else would you find
a traitor like this?
I'm only telling you, Mom.
This is a secret,
but I like Kim Jeong-geun.
I might even marry him.
Why?
Why do you like Jeong-geun?
He's cute. He's the cutest
in our neighborhood.
Goodness.
Geum-myeong, you're a big girl now.
There's even a boy you like.
But you know,
I wish you'd grow up a little slower.
Just a little slower.
Why?
You're adorable right now.
You're just so adorable.
Geum-myeong.
Even when you grow up,
promise to tell me
lots of your secrets, okay?
Of course, you're my secret keeper.
Really?
You're my best friend, Mom.
Even more than Kim Jeong-geun?
Goodness.
Mom, who's your best friend?
Mine? You're my best friend.
Then who do you like?
I like Yang Gwan-sik.
More than me?
No, you're my favorite
in the whole wide world.
Actually, you're my favorite too.
Really?
Yeah, that's why I bought Popeye
for a snack.
Because you said Popeye was your favorite.
My favorite snack is Apollo.
Oh my. That's why you bought Popeye?
I decided not to buy Apollo
because I love you.
My goodness.
POPEYE
Thank you.
That makes me so happy.
We used to be each other's world.
One left that world,
while the other stayed behind.
What should I make for you later?
I'll make anything.
I want jangjorim.
Jangjorim?
My mom still stayed in the world
where her sweetest secret keeper was.
How can the two of us eat all this?
Where's the fun in eating these?
She works, so it must be hard for her
to visit us over the weekend.
She'd be tired too.
After receiving about a thousand calls
from home asking if I'd eaten,
I felt a strong hunger.
Mom, I'm hungry.
I started craving Mom's cooking.
Baby.
How did you manage to come? How?
I took a vacation.
You should've called me.
It's late already.
I'm hungry.
Yeah, we have food.
I'll whip up some fresh rice in no time.
Baby.
I made a whole pot of jangjorim.
Your dad has been peeling quail eggs
for you since yesterday.
That's right. Chonggak kimchi!
It's well-fermented now.
You like it sour, don't you?
Eun-myeong likes it fresh,
and you like it sour.
I always have to make it separately.
You're just killing me, you are.
The floor's cold. It's cold.
I actually knew it already.
How quiet the house must have been
until just five minutes ago,
and how lonely they must have been.
All right.
If you had called,
I would have gone to the airport.
So you can show up an hour early
like last time?
Go back to sleep after you eat, okay?
Are you feeding a pig?
As a kid, after I fell and cried,
they would give me candy.
Mom, I don't eat broccoli.
It's for digestion.
Let's have some nice,
simple noodles for lunch.
Here.
You call this simple?
Then what does "not simple" look like?
After I recovered from the mumps,
they bought me a pork cutlet.
Come on, you love spicy noodles.
Geum-myeong!
Steamed buns!
You love red beans.
For their heartbroken daughter,
they once again focused
on doing just one thing.
That's right.
Yeah, she just showed up out of the blue.
Obviously, she missed her mom.
That's right, you punk.
Amberjack!
Real amberjack.
Is there fake amberjack?
Against all odds,
they raised me yet again.
Dad, I'm going to gain weight.
Wow, it's amberjack.
They made sure not a pound of me
disappeared from the world.
Really? Okay.
-It's freezing.
-Wow, your brother wants to talk to you.
What? You miss me
now that you're in the military?
"Oh, Sister!"
So you got dumped, huh?
He dumped you, didn't he?
"Oh, Yeong-beom…"
In the fortress
that was both comforting and unsettling,
I slept well and recharged,
just like a bear hibernating for winter.
Geum-myeong.
What is it?
You want to sleep more?
Do you really have to sleep more?
What?
Wake up.
What is it?
Let's go somewhere together.
We can just go later.
Dad, I'm tired!
Go back to sleep.
Why did that thought cross my mind
at that moment?
When I went on trips with Yeong-beom,
I used to jump out of bed at 4:00 a.m.
You knew I'd get up, didn't you?
Why did he put a life jacket on me?
GEUMEUNDONG
Aren't you fishing?
-It's my day off.
-You?
Apparently, there are no clouds.
It's coming now. There it is.
You woke me up to see the sunrise?
You know the new Sunrise Condo
by the Sunrise Restaurant?
You have to pay 30,000 won a night
to see it from there.
But you're seeing it for free,
thanks to your dad.
I'll just pay 30,000 won too.
Pay me, then.
Seeing the sunrise gives you energy.
When I see the sunrise,
I pray no matter what.
For you all to do well,
I just pray every single day.
You see the sunrise every single day?
Are you out here at this time every day?
Don't you want to sleep in?
Who in the world doesn't want to sleep in?
So why is yours the only boat
that sets out so early every day?
How do you live like this every day?
Maybe if I sleep less,
you two can sleep more.
That just wakes me up.
Now that I think about it,
there's never been a day
when Dad woke up later than I did.
Don't you have any hand cream?
Wow, your mom only packed things you love.
The rolled omelet is yours though.
Your mom is so excited to cook for you.
Doesn't it get scary?
It's scary.
There's nothing in the world
as scary as the ocean.
So you just put up with it?
Even if you're scared?
When the wind is fierce and I get scared,
that's what I look at.
The lighthouse?
No.
You see that tiny light over there?
It's the light of a fishing boat.
I just look at that.
Thinking that the boat must feel
lonely and scared like me
makes it less scary.
Thinking about going together
makes it manageable.
Mom and I are always
sailing a boat by your side.
If you're ever hungry,
don't think twice and come home.
Dad.
You're embarrassed, huh?
How do you face the neighborhood?
You already gave out the invitations.
Not at all. I'd be more embarrassed
if you married into that family.
I knew you wouldn't marry him.
I know everything.
You do everything well,
so it'll all go well.
You always say that.
If you say so, does everything go well?
What else can I do
other than say these words?
If you were born into a richer,
more successful family instead of mine,
they would've done everything,
all kinds of things for you
and made sure you never got hurt.
Then don't be my dad in the next life.
Don't ever be my dad again.
-Don't go through all this trouble.
-What trouble?
I'm just happy.
Not once did I have trouble,
thanks to you.
Not even once.
You always give me 120 things
when you only have 100.
How can you give me more?
Don't ever bring up "rich dad."
I wouldn't trade you
for the richest man in the world.
I think that's cured my knees.
Just go to the hospital if you're in pain.
You think cooling patches fix everything?
Seriously, you're so annoying.
You're so annoying.
To be honest, I don't mind…
if you don't get married.
Actually, I like that better.
I'm going to get married.
You're always happy being married.
Why do you keep telling me not to?
That day, I saw a different sun.
Only after my sun,
the first to light up the lonely ocean,
had set forever…
did I realize how warm it was
to be by my dad's side.
Why are you getting off the boat?
I saw the sunrise with my dad.
What about your mom? Isn't she working?
It was just me and my dad.
-Just you two?
-Yes.
-Just the two of you?
-Yes!
Hey, do you study hard?
Dad, do you need help?
You look just like your mom.
Do you study hard?
-I'm actually working.
-Where?
-At a major corporation.
-Which one? Damn it.
Give it to me.
-You're setting sail on a Sunday?
-What's a Sunday for a seaman?
Hey, wear your shoes properly.
Why? Did your wife tell you
to go out again?
Again? Damn it! What do you even know?
What do you know about my family?
Every family has its own way.
He's so disrespectful.
-To someone else's dad.
-Hey!
Hey, he may be a captain now,
but he used to pull in the nets
and cook ramyeon for me, you hear me?
Well, in any case,
you're both captains now, aren't you?
Who said otherwise?
That brat Yang Eun-myeong
broke up with his daughter, right?
That family, seriously.
They are just… Damn it.
My husband
won't be working for you anymore.
He won't be working for you!
Fine. Then don't.
Please don't.
Why's she holding her dad's hand
at her age?
SANDGLASS
Well… what are you up to these days?
Are you running the store properly?
Is it makeup you're selling
or that ridiculous hairstyle?
You know,
If you've got time,
you and I can go out on a boat,
you know,
early in the morning…
Okay?
You know, when the sun rises, we can--
Hire somebody.
What?
I'm busy too.
Do you write to that boy or not? Do you?
If you visit him, you're dead meat.
-He won't see me even if I go.
-So you went?
You did, didn't you? You brat!
I can have him put in military prison!
A friend of mine is a general.
Really,
aren't you ashamed?
You what?
You go around meeting
every woman out there.
It's hilarious that you won't let me
date a single guy.
Goddamn it!
Seriously. What the hell do you know?
Your four kids witnessed it.
Shouting "Goddamn it" all the time
will never make us listen to you.
I should shave your hair off, you little--
Fine, go ahead and shave my head!
You've already ruined my life anyway.
See how you like it
when you're stuck with me forever.
Don't you dare slam that door on me!
It was the wind!
-Listen--
-What?
Too noisy again? Do you own this house?
And what the hell are you even studying?
It's about dinner.
Make whatever.
Actually,
can you eat out before coming home?
Why do you keep eating at home now?
It's uncomfortable for everyone.
Everyone? It's uncomfortable for everyone?
Why is it uncomfortable?
Raise your hand if it's uncomfortable!
T.O. I LOVE EUN-MYEONG
600KM APART, 6MM AT HEART
I WILL ALWAYS WAIT FOR YOU
I DO WAT I WANT
DON'T TELL ME WAT TO DO
You all get to eat white rice,
thanks to me!
You hear me? It's all thanks to me!
Apparently, their kumquat field
is around 10,000 to 17,000 ㎡.
That's quite a big difference,
10,000 ㎡ to 17,000 ㎡.
You know what they say
about the father of that family?
They call him Seogwipo's Yang Gwan-sik.
He's such a devoted husband.
But they actually have
more than a kumquat field.
I heard they own a mountain too.
That family owns a huge mountain.
Do you have a crush on the guy or what?
Why do you keep talking about
the kumquat man?
They have a kumquat field.
They own a mountain. They also have a son.
A public official.
He is 29 and went to a college in Seoul.
To know what a man is like,
you must look at his father.
They learn how to treat their family
from their father.
That's why Eun-myeong's
such a dating expert?
The kumquat man's son
looks like the actor Choi Jae-sung.
You need a handsome man.
You fight a lot less
if you marry a handsome one.
Mom, it's only been a year
since I broke off the engagement.
So what? Is it a crime or something?
The entire neighborhood knows.
Seeing someone else already?
How does that make me look?
So what if they know?
The entire neighborhood knows nothing.
-Why didn't you hand them out?
-Just because.
I had a feeling you'd call it off.
What?
That's how I raised you.
If she can't even ride that,
she'll spend her whole life
in the kitchen.
I want her to have everything.
And I want her to do everything,
every single thing she wants.
I don't want her to set the table.
I want her to be the one to flip it.
Geum-myeong.
You gotta pedal harder. Go on!
Keep having run rolling!
Keep rolling!
Why didn't you flip some tables yourself?
Weren't you angry that you couldn't?
Seven.
Eight.
Why were you always so nice?
Was there a prize for it?
ONE BASKET OF TANGERINES
80 WON FOR TEN
That's 11.
-What?
-Eleven.
It was because of you.
Right.
Because of you.
You were looking at me
with those sweet, twinkling eyes.
How could I just live as I please?
When I held you guys after I gave birth,
this is what I thought to myself.
"From now on, my life will become
the stories my children remember
when they grow up."
"The stories my children will reminisce
about when they come to my funeral."
Once I realized that,
I couldn't bring myself
to live a single day dishonestly.
"The eldest child
of Yang Gwan-sik and Oh Ae-sun."
I think I kind of understood
why that was written on the invitation.
I was their Geum-myeong.
Geum-myeong.
You did nothing wrong. You avoided
a pile of crap because of your luck.
Yeong-beom isn't a pile of crap.
And I know.
You don't have to tell me for me to know.
You're crying on the inside.
When you were a child,
Kim Jeong-geun
didn't want to sit next to you,
and you cried for four days.
How do you even remember his name?
How can I forget it?
It's a secret my secret keeper
told only me.
Think of it as wrapping something precious
and tucking it away
in a warm spot on the floor.
Okay?
Once in a while, it'd be nostalgic
to take it out and look at it.
They say your first love
is meant to be a memory.
How would you know?
You live with your first love.
Live with the joy you had
riding your bike when you were a kid.
It'd be a waste
to miss out on the fun now.
My goodness.
Your hands are still so young.
Just like freshly bloomed petals.
Flower petals.
It'd be a waste for you too.
You should do something.
Write poems.
I write every day.
My poetry collection is over there.
1995 HOUSEHOLD ACCOUNT BOOK
OH AE-SUN
Just like an old garment is turned
into new clothes by a skilled tailor…
I went there like a rag,
but I came back neat and sharp.
She was only here for a few days,
but the house just feels so empty now.
Well, it's always been just the two of us.
Seriously, my goodness.
She should buy things for herself, not us.
She's so caring.
She's just way too caring.
FOR THE FOOD
WRITE YOUR POEM
I received so much,
yet my smallest gesture made us even.
That's how unfair we were.
Goodness, my bones.
The cold makes my bones ache
more and more.
Oh my.
What kind of debt must one owe
to be born a mother?
Our elder went into the water
even past the age of 80
but passed away
without a single intact undergarment.
Her kids chipped away
at the money in their old mom's hands,
yet they couldn't see
it was the price of her life?
They took all from their mother's life
yet cried like devoted children.
But she said she broke even
because even a president might end up
in a prison uniform,
but at least she made a living
on her own until the end.
Oh my.
Not even a dog would steal
a haenyeo's fortune.
The problem lies in one's character,
not one's fortune.
Ae-sun also needs to toughen up.
She feels sorry for everyone,
so she's always broke.
Should I go stop her?
Let her be.
Once we leave this life,
Ae-sun won't have her aunts or friends.
How long can we stand up for her?
Make sure she stands without backup.
Well, at least I don't just take it.
I fight back.
Come on.
Why can't you just live well, just well?
That's why, from the very start,
no one has a fate like yours.
You have a husband
who's a complete fool for you,
a top-university daughter,
and the haenyeo bullies
just gave you a good spot.
-Hey, I'm right here.
-That's not all.
Your sister-in-law
takes care of your parents-in-law.
I wondered when she'd boast about that.
By principle, why should I look after Mom
when she has an older son?
You think you're taking care of her?
You sold off your parents' house
for your business.
Now you're turning your elderly mom
into a maid to look after your children.
"Taking care"? As if.
My mom hates that auntie the most.
When you were a child,
Ae-sun fed you three meals a day.
You should be repaying her
for raising you.
You think Ae-sun's pocket is yours?
What's your problem?
What the hell did you bring?
Why did you bring that mat?
ELVAN WELLNESS MAT
Ae-sun, if Gwan-sik sleeps on that,
it will help his knees heal
and even prevent cancer.
It's actually more expensive,
but I'm not here to profit from family.
I think of you first
when I see something good.
If Gwan-sik places his crooked fingers
on the hot mat, the infrared--
What are you doing? This isn't refundable.
Mother also has back pain, right?
Don't lie and say you bought it for her.
Tell her it's from me.
If I'm spending money,
I might as well boast about it.
You're making me embarrassed.
Go. Just go.
Please come empty-handed next time.
Ae-sun. Your personality
determines your fate, right?
What, are you going to say
my fate is good again?
Look.
You took all my money again today.
Eat one more.
Just one more!
Goodness, what a lousy fate I have.
Who knew I'd be cleaning up after
my grandchild past the age of 60?
Unplug it when you're not using it.
It'll catch fire.
Whenever he catches a cold,
that damn Gyeong-ok blames me
for how I dressed him.
This is worse than looking after in-laws.
-Hey!
-Seo Dong-min!
Stand at attention! Attention, now!
Why sit there
if you're not going to say anything?
Just go. Go home to your wife.
No one's ever been on my side
my entire life.
So, how's your back?
Just mind your wife's back.
Stop using patches and go get acupuncture.
I'll take you there and back.
Yeah, right.
Well, I guess
I've always been biased--
Even a staunch nationalist
wouldn't be as biased as you
in a Korea-Japan match.
Well, listen…
I wouldn't trade you
for the richest man in the world.
for Korea's most celebrated mother.
Lift your foot!
Why would she want to be your mom?
Doesn't she have a preference?
No daughter-in-law can truly be filial
with a filial son,
and no mother-in-law can tolerate
a son foolishly devoted to his wife.
Even the most celebrated mother
would turn her back on you.
Give it to me.
What's an ungrateful son for?
At least he can do this.
Who said you're an ungrateful son?
Who said that?
Didn't you say you should've raised dogs?
The whole neighborhood knows.
Tell them to stop talking crap.
You've been a filial son too.
I know what it's like to lose parents
but not a child.
Staying alive was the real filial duty.
Who wouldn't know that?
Mom, look.
It's Jong-gu.
Your eldest grandson, Jong-gu, is here.
Grandma, it's me, Jong-gu.
You don't even recognize Jong-gu?
Jong-gu, the stupid idiot.
Mom, you taught Jong-gu to read and write.
He didn't even know his times tables then,
but he grew up to be a card shark.
Sister, you know who I am?
Who am I?
Come on, sister.
Dear me.
My mom once mastered
the Korean and Chinese alphabets,
but she's totally lost her sharpness.
How come it's her mind
that crosses the river first?
-Hello, Ae-sun.
-You're here, Ae-sun.
Come on in.
When did you come all the way?
I thought I might never celebrate
my sister's birthday again.
I came just in case this is the last one.
Grandma, I'm here.
She doesn't know.
She doesn't recognize anyone.
Ae-sun, this is really upsetting me.
Goodness.
Grandma.
Grandma, I brought you senbei snacks. See?
After you finish your meal--
Of course I know.
Han-gyu's daughter.
My son Han-gyu's daughter.
You…
Have you been well?
So I've always been
Han-gyu's daughter to you?
You forget my name
but remember that I'm Han-gyu's daughter?
Does that make you sad?
No, I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
What is it?
Is something bothering you?
What is it that's bothering you?
What is it?
Is something bothering you?
Nothing's bothering me. Nothing at all.
So what if it is?
Will you buy her another boat?
Just one word
about Han-gyu's daughter's struggle,
and my mom just went ahead
and got her a whole boat.
Mother, I'm struggling too.
Your 60-year-old daughter-in-law
is struggling too.
-Please get me a boat too.
-Stop it.
Grandma.
Do you want to come live with me now?
No.
Come live with us.
I don't want to.
You know Gwan-sik is so caring.
He'll do anything I ask him.
No.
Why not?
Not your house.
Why? Because we are two generations apart?
Grandma, I'll get you dentures
in the spring.
I can cash in my savings plan then.
I'll make sure you get dentures with that.
You? Dentures for me?
Yeah.
You also helped me get new teeth
when I was a child.
Gap-toothed little pup
Don't go near the waters
You'll scare the baby fish
Don't go near the magpie
Caw, caw, they will badmouth you
Let's see.
I won't pull it just yet.
Let me just check if the thread is hooked.
Liar. You say that,
but you'll still pull it out.
You're so smart, just like your dad.
Let's pull that tooth.
That crow is waiting for your tooth.
Wait a moment. Let me count to ten.
It won't hurt. It won't hurt at all.
Pull his tooth first.
His tooth is wobbly too.
Let me see how much it hurts.
His parents can pull his out.
Why do you have a thread on your tooth?
Go get your tooth pulled at home.
You came here to sell hairtail.
Why are you getting a tooth pulled?
Gwan-sik, you do it first.
You try it first.
Can you see if it hurts or not?
Aren't you scared?
So you aren't scared?
My clever little girl.
Where did you pick up
this cute little fool?
Good job.
Huh? Did you pull it?
It didn't hurt, did it?
There comes a season for everyone
when they lose their second tooth.
When did my gap-toothed little pup
grow so big?
The crows won't bring you
new teeth anymore.
I should take care of them.
I know something's bothering you.
I know how you feel.
I know exactly how you feel.
I also want to call out his name loudly
at least once…
and cry my heart out.
After holding it in all my life,
it's now hard for me…
to even say Han-gyu's name.
So I feel even more sorry.
I know
how you feel.
I know exactly how you feel.
"I know exactly how you feel."
Those words
brought Mom to her grandma's lap…
where she cried for a long time.
Why won't you go with her?
She's the daughter
of your favorite son, Han-gyu.
I wonder how much she paid for this.
Why? Do you find it harder
to ask your granddaughter for favors?
Or because of grandson-in-law?
This mat is expensive, isn't it?
You bought her a boat,
so why feel uncomfortable?
Go and enjoy
your granddaughter's food for once.
I couldn't even raise her myself.
I couldn't even feed her a whole croaker
when she was little.
How can I go live there?
You just can't forget
about the damn croakers.
You used to share your croakers
with her all the time!
Oh dear.
Once I get up there,
all that's waiting for me
is Han-Gyu's scolding.
All that's waiting for me
is a scolding from my child.
So warm and cozy.
I think I'm going to sleep well.
Oh my, Mother.
You look like a new bride.
Your children will remember you
by this photo, so pink looks great, right?
Did I live well?
Did I pay off my debt?
You did plenty.
Immeasurably so.
I'm out of breath.
Really out of breath from it all.
You must be gasping for air, right?
So,
was it a picnic or an ordeal?
Definitely a picnic.
I got to see all my children.
It was an unbelievable picnic.
I can't believe it.
KIM CHUN-OK OF GIMHAE KIM CLAN
MAY YOU FINALLY BE REUNITED
Every season in life is full of farewells.
Right?
No one arrives,
and all I see
is people leaving one by one.
Father, Mom.
Your grandmother, your father.
You were right, Mother.
My daughter-in-law was a cut above yours.
Right?
Dear me, I brought three spoons again.
Auntie Chung-su.
My grandmother.
You should've gotten dentures
before you left.
And…
Still, let's leave this world together.
Okay?
We thought we came to the picnic together,
but each had their own tide.
Just as the tides ebb and flow,
some have left,
but for some…
He's here.
The door's open. It's open.
…it was the season
for a new arrival at the picnic.
Oh dear, you must've been through so much.
Eun-myeong, I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you so much, my son.
Why are you just standing there?
Come on in.
I made all kinds of things for you.
You want to give us a salute
before coming in?
Salute?
Wait, why do you have so many things?
Mother.
Fine. Go ahead.
Did you bring something?
What is it?
Hello.
Oh my.
Hi, Hyeon-suk.
You're Bu Hyeon-suk.
My goodness, you guys are…
You guys are still seeing each other.
What now?
What do you want to do?
What…
Why are you putting your hand there?
You're scaring me.
Hyeon-suk, what are you doing?
Mother, Father.
What?
I don't wanna hear it.
You're Grandpa and Grandma now.
Oh my God.
You're Strikey's grandmother.
New sprouts still lift their heads
even in the frozen soil
of the front lines.
These punks…
A winter, as early as their spring,
was on its way.
You little punk,
you were sent to serve your country.
Ms. Yang!
Yang Geum-myeong!
Taiji, don't retire!
Taiji, please!
Taiji!
Geum-myeong!
A glistening winter,
as dazzling as spring, was on its way.
A GLISTENING WINTER
"JUST GET READY AND GO,
RIDE THE MOMENT WITH ALL YOU HAVE."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang